

# **TEEMU HOLAPPA**

INFORMATION PROCESSING SCIENCE STUDENT

#### PROFILE

Extremely motivated and hard working 23-year old Information Processing science student. Open to new challenges and ideas which also affects teamwork positively.

Constantly trying to find new challenges and overcome those, because that rewards me. My goal is to get more responsibility project by project. In the future i would like to work with Al.

#### CONTACT

- teemu.holappa97@gmail.com
- 044-5435425 (+358)
- in /HolaTeemu
- /HolaTeemu

## EDUCATION

09/2019 -

Information Processing Science, University of Oulu

- 150/300 credits by 05/2021

09/2013 - 06/2016 Upper secondary school graduate, Muhoksen lukio

#### SKILLS

## **Programming languages:**

- Python
- Java
- C
- SQL
- HTML + CSS

## Languages (writing and speech):

- Finnish: Native language
- English: Fluent
- Swedish: Satisfactory

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Work trial + substitute teacher (Elementary school)**

**AUTUMN 2017 - SPRING 2019** 

 After work trial I worked as a substitute teacher approximately 225 hours

#### **Construction assistant, Sihti Oulu Oy**

08/2018 - 03/2019

 Helping in construction sites in basically everything that needed to be done. Also worked as a mover.

## **Personal assistant, City of Oulu**

06/2015 - 08/2015

 Helped in basic daily tasks, for example cooking, cleaning, babysitting etc.

#### REFEREES

Toni Väyrynen, Principal, Hyrkin koulu 044-4970449, toni.vayrynen@muhos.fi

Jukka Laine, Principal, Korivaaran koulu 044-4970430, jukka.laine@muhos.fi